

PEDRO GABRIEL CAIRES

Fullstack Developer

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Hello world! My name is Pedro Gabriel and I'm a Fullstack Web and Mobile developer.

MY STORY

I started programming when I was 14, I've always been a hardware and software lover, when I started to attend the Technician School in Computer Science it was a big definitive push into the area. In 2020, along with two long time friends, I created Phog Tech, a freelance team specialized in Web solutions. After that I participated in several Open Source projects and now I currently work at Simbiose Social, a social tech company. I stand out for my agility with new technologies and the ease of solving problems.

SKILLS

- Javascript (React Native, Node.js & others)
 - PHP (Laravel, Codelgniter & others)
 - MySQL (& other relational databases)
 - Java
 - Kotlin
 - Flutter
 - Semantic HTML, CSS/SASS
 - Python
 - Docker
 - SOLID
 - AWS (& other cloud solutions)
 - Scrum/Kanban

EDUCATION

- "Curso Técnico em Informática" at Eniac College (2019~2021)
- College in Information Systems at FIAP (2022~Present)

CONTACT

Cell Phone: +55 11 986341150 Email: pedrogcs0104@gmail.com

LINKS

GITHUB: https://github.com/dgtyPedro

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/pedrogabriel-caires/

EXPERIENCE

PHOG TECH

PHP Back-End Developer (2020~2021)

I was responsible for structuring and developing all back-end of the projects that the team was hired.

I'M LABS

Fullstack Developer (2021~2022)

An excellent opportunity in which on different projects I was exposed to several new and different technologies. I made several projects with ViteJs, NextJs, Laravel, Python, React Native and other technologies.

SIMBIOSE SOCIAL

Fullstack Developer (2022~Present)

The company I currently work for. I'm a "jack of all trades" type developer that creates features from the front-end to the back-end along with database structuring. I work extensively with Laravel, React.js, and MySQL.

NOTABLE PROJECTS

- Simbiose's Platform: Platform that connects companies with NGOs made in ReactJs. LINK: https://simbiose.social
- Volumes & Markings: Measure application for liquid containers made 100% by me in React Native.

LINK: <u>play.google.com/store/apps/details?</u> <u>id=com.dooguitryx.volumesandmarkings</u>

- dumpi-fy: Spotify playlist manager made 100% by me in PHP.

LINK: https://dumpi-fy.herokuapp.com